with a favorable safety profile we're on track now for the fda approval in the first
subtype of cindu and fda submission of the other two types in the second half
now building on the overall profile for rhapsody when you look at the next slide uh slide 14 we did
release as well the phase two results uh for remy brutinib in food allergy to support a fast acting
oral option for these patients we also have are on track now to initiate the phase three study you
can see here on the left the data that we we read out the 100 milligram dose uh provided 86.7
results our modeling indicates that the 75 milligram eid would be the appropriate dose
for the uh patients moving forward so that's the dose we've taken forward into the the phase three
study uh our focus will be a multi-allergen uh prevention study so i think that's really
exciting across a broad range of age 12 years all the way up to 65 years and as i mentioned
anticipate initiation in the second half this has the potential to address a significant unmet need
risk eligible patients across major markets so very excited to add this to the indication list
hopefully for rhapsody then moving to slide 15. also in the quarter we completed the acquisition
of avidity adding three late stage medicines for neuromuscular disease and i just wanted to
highlight two data points from from the quarter we did release the one-year results for del zoda
our for our dmd exxon 44 skipping medicine which was presented at the muscular dystrophy
association to a standing ovation which i think shows the impact that this medicine could have
for these patients uh you can see here the creatine kinase declines which uh are remarkable uh and
you can i think really experts have have opined that it's really a revolution with this medicine
we're excited to also build after this a range of additional exxon skipping medicines for dmd
we are expecting the submission now in the first half as we've worked through some of the
additional cmc topics
make sure that the file is fully submission ready and then with uh del disaran we had the final
results for the phase one two study marina trial published in the new england journal those are
results you all know well but i think highlight the excellent profile that we've seen with this
medicine and we're on track for the phase three readout for the harbor study in the second half